qe.com.qa 2010-09-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Qatar Exchange (QE) takes reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. This Privacy Statement describes how your personal information is collected, used, shared and safeguarded by QE.

QE protects personal information provided by you through the use of this website. QE is not responsible for the privacy practices of non- QE web sites linked to this site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other web sites when you leave our Web site.

QE collects personal information from you to provide requested services and enhance your customer experience. We may supplement the information collected from you with information that is available from publicly available third party sources.

QE is the sole owner of the information collected on this website, and will not sell, share, or rent your personal information in ways different from what is disclosed in this privacy statement. QE also uses third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. QE has no control over third-party cookies. QE does share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers, in ways that do not directly identify you.
